#### Contact

d.z.dimaquibo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/darryl-z-dimaquibo-rn (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Hospitals Public Health

#### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A) ACLS BLS

#### **Publications**

Adsorption of Eu(III) onto Roots of Water Hyacinth

# Darryl Z. Dimaquibo

Registered Nurse, CCRN® - Adult

San Marcos, California

### Summary

I am a Registered Nurse (RN), licensed to practice in California, from the Palomar College RN Program in San Marcos, CA (San Diego County).

I am a member of the Scripps Health team at the Prebys Cardiovascular Institute on the Scripps Memorial Hospital La Jolla Campus in the Cardiovascular Intensive Care Unit (CVICU). Prior to that, I served in the Site Based Float Pool (SBFP) at Scripps Memorial Hospital La Jolla & Scripps Green Hospital - Intensive Care Units. I also work, on a per Diem basis, in utilization and case management in addition to critical care.

I got my start as a New Graduate Nurse Resident at Palomar Health in the CVICU/Medical Intensive Care Unit (ICU)/Critical Care Unit (CCU) and worked my way up to Clinical Nurse II at Palomar Health in the with experience as a psychiatric RN.

## Experience

Scripps Health

1 year 9 months

Registered Nurse

April 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Scripps Memorial Hospital La Jolla, Prebys Cardiovascular Institute

- Proficient managing mechanical ventilation, titrating sedation and vasoactive drips, arterial and invasive lines, patients with CHF, sternal precautions, immediate post-operative open-heart surgical care, sepsis, CVA with tPA administration, and other critically ill patients.
- Timely and accurately documentation in Electronic Health Record (Epic).
- Collaborate with intensivists, fellow RNs, and other members of the multidisciplinary team to provide individualized treatment and care of critically ill patients towards expected outcomes.

Registered Nurse

#### October 2018 - April 2019 (7 months)

Scripps Memorial La Jolla & Scripps Green

 Site Based Float Pool (SBFP) RN for Scripps Memorial Hospital La Jolla and Scripps Green in the Cardiovascular ICU (CVICU), Neurosurgery-Trauma ICU (NST-ICU) and Green ICU, based on site requirements to provide safe and effective care to critically ill patients.

#### AURORA BEHAVIORAL HEALTH CARE SAN DIEGO

Registered Nurse (Utilization Review) - Per Diem December 2019 - Present (7 months)

Greater San Diego Area

- Provides ongoing case management to patients
- · Attends treatment team meetings weekly
- Assists in the development and implementation of treatment plans
- Communicates with referral sources and other appropriate parties regarding patients' progress
- Coordinates and implements patients' discharge
- Attends and participates in departmental, other clinical, and administrative meetings
- Supports maintenance and development of clinical program or services
- Maintains effective communication with all necessary departments.

#### Palomar Health

1 year 3 months

Registered Nurse (Float) - Crisis Stabilization Unit June 2018 - October 2018 (5 months)

Escondido, California

Provide safe care for and thorough assessment of adult psychiatric patients in crisis in preparation for inpatient admission and treatment or transition to outpatient follow up for safe discharge.

Registered Nurse - Intensive Care Unit August 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 3 months)

Escondido, California

- Provide safe and effective care of critically ill patients in the 24-bed CVICU/ MICU. Cross-trained in Trauma Intensive Care Unit.
- Proficient managing mechanical ventilation, titrating sedation and vasoactive drips, arterial and invasive lines, and sternal precautions in patients with CHF, recent post-operative open-heart care, sepsis, CVA with tPA administration, and other critically ill patients.
- Active member and contributor in the Unit Practice Council.

- Document in Electronic Health Record (Cerner).
- Daily collaboration with intensivists, fellow RNs, and other members of the multi-disciplinary team to provide individualized treatment and care of critically ill patients.

Aurora Behavioral Health Care 5 years 10 months

Registered Nurse July 2017 - May 2018 (11 months)

Greater San Diego Area

To deliver quality general and psychiatric nursing care to patients with psychiatric or emotional disorders; to serve actively and constructively as a member of the organization's multi-disciplinary treatment team, and support the organization's and adults psychiatric philosophy of care.

#### **Essential Duties:**

- Collects and analyzes data regarding patient's physical, psychological, selfcare, educational experiences, and anticipating discharge planning needs
- Develops a comprehensive outline of care to be delivered to attain expected outcomes; includes in this plan, specific goals and interventions delineating nursing actions unique to each patient
- Maintains effective communication with all units and departments
- Functions within the policies and philosophies of the organization
- · Supervises direct patient care as required
- · Works within budgetary constraints to include staff overtime and supplies
- Carries out medication management responsibilities
- Conducts patient community meetings
- Provides input into discharge planning process
- Maintain patient, and unit related documentation
- Maintain a safe, orderly, and therapeutic environment for patients.

Behavioral Health Specialist August 2012 - July 2017 (5 years)

To provide direct patient care to geriatric, adult, adolescent, or child patients with psychiatric disorders; to ensure the safety and well-being of these patients; to support the maintenance of therapeutic milieu.

#### **Essential Duties:**

- Participate in input and follow through with regard to treatment planning
- Observe and identify patients problems, needs and strengths, and suggest treatment plan modifications
- Provide input on, and implement patient discharge plans
- Accompany and transport patients as assigned
- · Facilitate patient community meetings
- Maintain patient, and unit related documentation
- Admit new patients to the unit, program and milieu
- Maintain a safe, orderly, and therapeutic environment for patients
- Assists patients with daily living activities consistent with treatment plans
- Carry out administrative and clerical assignments to support patient care, and organizational operations.

Palomar College Nursing Student August 2015 - May 2017 (1 year 10 months) San Marcos, California

To receive academic and clinical training in preparation for licensure as a Registered Nurse.

Teng & Associates
Mechanical Designer, EIT
December 2007 - January 2009 (1 year 2 months)

To provide mechanical design and architectural services, which include HVAC design, drawings, layouts, bills-of-materials, energy efficiency studies, life-cycle analysis, etc.

US Navy Hospital Corpsman November 2005 - November 2007 (2 years 1 month) Twentynine Palms, California

I worked in the Pediatric Clinic at Naval Hospital Twentynine Palms (NHTP). My duties included assisting pediatricians and nurses with patient procedures, administering immunizations and vaccines, front-desk service (patient checkin, telephones, information), etc. I was honorably discharged.

Apple Retail
Mac Specialist
November 2004 - May 2005 (7 months)

To assist customers in finding a solution for their computing and entertainment needs within the Apple line of products by providing them information about the product(s), tailored to them, that best addressed their needs.

#### Sport Chalet

Footwear Expert

December 2003 - December 2004 (1 year 1 month)

To assist customers in selecting proper equipment for their needs in footwear, mountain shop and general athletics. Engaged in training new employees and schedule-writing. To serve as a substitute bookkeeper.

## Education

Palomar College

ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

University of California San Diego

BSMech.E, Mechanical Engineering · (1998 - 2003)

Northern Arizona University

NASA Sharp Plus - High School Apprenticeship Program · (1997 - 1997)

**Texas Southern University** 

NASA Sharp Plus - High School Apprenticeship Program · (1996 - 1996)